The kettle and the idol
Now, let's go to the main project.
Please give the title call to ℃-ute.
My three-step element.
Yay!
Now, this is the corner where you will be introduced to the three elements that make up Mizuki.
We would like to learn more about our guest idols.
So please tell us about the three elements.
Yes, I will.
Here we go.
The first one is?
Mr. Popper.
Let me ask you to say three things.
The first is Mr. Popper.
The second one is "one by one," and the third one is "various ahs.
The third one is "various ahs.
Wanne shittotsu ne!
Poppa!
Popper-san calls the fans of Crown Pop "Popper-san.
I would say that Mr. Popper has been a great pillar of support for me.
I wrote this first entry because I feel that Popper is a pillar of support for me.
I have seen him at events.
I have seen him at events, and he is very kind to the musicians.
They are very kind.
I myself like idols a lot, and I have been to many of them as a customer.
I used to go to many events as a customer.
I had only seen it from the fans' point of view.
But I knew that the fans were kind.
I see.
If you don't mind my asking, what kind of places did you go to?
Stardust idols.
I don't have to contact Stardust at all anymore.
I really like Stardust idols.
I like Stardust idols, like 3BJr.
I also often go to Takoyaki Rainbow.
3BJr.'s penlights were star-shaped.
My mom, sister and I loved them.
My father used to listen to their songs.
We often went to live shows together.
We often went to live shows together, so each of us took one of those star-shaped penlights with us.
I also went to those idol shows.
I felt like I wanted to try it myself.
I felt that idols are such sparkling beings.
I also felt that the fans were so happy to see their idols.
I also felt how happy the fans looked when they saw their idols.
I also felt how happy the fans were to see their idols, how they seemed to be enjoying talking about their favorite idols, how they were watching the live performances, how they seemed to be enjoying themselves
I saw them live, and I felt like I was on the stage.
I want to be someone who can bring a smile to someone and make them happy.
I wanted to be someone who can bring smiles to people's faces and make them happy by bringing them love.
I wanted to be an idol.
But were you nervous at first, Mr. Popper?
I was nervous at my first live performance.
I thought I wouldn't be able to look my fans in the eye.
But it wasn't like that. They looked at me very kindly, even though it was my first time and I wasn't doing well at all.
They looked at me very kindly, and their eyes were warm.
I felt strongly that I wanted to be someone who could make them happy, and I wanted to return the favor.
I felt that I would like to return the favor.
Thank you very much for watching.
I have been saying to Kagami, "Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry," and doing things.
I have recently realized that I often do things like saying, "Don't worry, it's okay" to Kagami.
This program is a good example of that.
Yay! Takuya
Katsu-san
Ise! Mr. Kiarinofu
Mr. Iwajan
Mr. Pakta
Thank you very much for your kind attention!
I hope you and Miya will always be in love!
Thank you very much for your support!